Hello
Hello friends Welcome to Taste Rice Now
friends in today's video we will
talk about two companies one is
HDFC Limited and the other is
HDFC Bank I want to make one thing clear first
I will not
do any fundamental analysis in this video nor any
technical one I would just
like to keep my perspective I will share with you what I personally think
about both the companies
and whatever doubts you have in your mind,
whatever confusion, doubt etc. or
you can call it fear, whatever you have, I will try to
clear them all in today's video
just a few days ago news
of merger of HDFC Limited and HDFC Bank
came as soon as that news came
both these stocks saw a huge boom
and seeing that many
people entered in it and right now they are
stuck at the upper level because
correction has started coming in both these stocks,
correction will come because this was
not a normal growth, this Shahrukh has come
back to where it started from now I
would like to ask you a question when you entered in HDFC
Limited or HDFC Bank or
both  What did you think when you
entered? I mean, did you use logic
behind entering? The stock price is going up, so
we'll enter here, then the
stock price will come down here. We'll escape from here
and take the profit in between. So,
I would like to say that this thinking is wrong,
this logic itself is wrong. This is not how things work in the stock market.
Professionals do
n't work like this. Two things have to be
kept in mind here. Before entering any stock, there are
two processes.
Entry into any stock is done only after following them.
First, you have to check the fundamentals.
If you
want to enter any stock for the long term, then
second, you have to read the technical charts. If
you want to enter any stock for the short term, then
short term means
intraday swing trading, position trading.
All this is not short term.
Apart from fundamentals and technicals, there is no third
technique or process in shares. Now
tell me, when you entered these stocks,
which of these two processes did you follow? If
not any of them, then with great sadness I would say that
you are relying on fate.  When
money is invested, it is
called gambling. I know my
words may sound harsh,
but my friend, this is the only harsh thing that happens.
In today's video, you will learn a lot about how you can make a profit in
your
entire life through the share market. So, don't take it to heart.
Professionals. Now the question is, we
are useless in the northern city. Now, what do you have to do? I will do
some questions and answers in this, and you will get
your answer. The first question is, do you urgently need the money you
invested in this company right now?
If not, then
fold these two companies.
This is a company. If you need a part of this money, then
I
would like to tell you that the money you need, that is, the money you will
need in a few days.
Never invest such money in the share market relying on luck,
otherwise you will regret it a lot or you will have to
book a loss, otherwise the money will remain stuck for a
few days, maybe for a few months, maybe for a
few years. In such a situation, if the
company is good, then you will get your money back
with profit later, but if the
company is bad, then the entire money can be wasted.
But the good news is that both these
companies are very good companies. One is
HDFC Bank, the king of the banking sector,
and the other is HDFC Bank's parent company,
HDFC Limited, the king of the anywhere sector.
Therefore, if you need this money in an emergency, if you do
n't get this money, it wo
n't work. If there is such a situation, then only you
can book it in loss because
in the short term you can still go away. And if there is
no such situation, even if you don't withdraw this money, it will still be fine. So let it be. If
you have both the stocks, then
call both of them. If there is one, then find a solution.
Because HDFC Bank and HDFC
Limited are not companies that can be sold at a loss.
This company has been formed now for long term holding.
Now I would like to ask another question
for those people who are afraid
that their money might get lost. So
I would like to ask you people, why are you
afraid? You are the owner of this company, even if it is a
small share, but you are the owner. The
fundamentals of your company are very strong, you have
no need to be afraid. You know there is a
saying in the share market.  In a2b, if it is
not there in the portfolio then what will remain,
S2 means HDFC Bank HDFC Limited,
you mean Bajaj Finance and Bajaj
Finserv, so if you have these two or you do
not have one then there is
no need to be afraid, rather I would say that
both these stocks and your portfolio will definitely
come, right now there has been a slight
decline, otherwise it would have
made a profit right now, but there is no need to worry,
in a few days when everything will be fine
then the profit will definitely increase, I would like to say two things in points, you will be able to come,
whenever you
invest money in any company in the share market,
then definitely check the fundamentals of that company,
if you enter for the long term
and if you want to enter for the short term
in any stock, then definitely
follow the technical, you will definitely read the chart pattern
and definitely maintain a stop loss,
this is great, if you do
not know how to do fundamentals, do not know how to do technical advisory, then
learn, it has been proved that
you have entered the field with sitting posture
but you do not know how to play cricket  And what's more, I do
n't even know the role of the gym. I don't have a helmet, there is no
guard, and a fast bowler is
standing in front of you, and you are trying to chant Vallabh Bhaja in the air. You
know what will happen, either you will get out or you will be sent
straight to the hospital.
You will learn to do fundamental analysis and technical analysis.
Your money will be lost in the share market. By the way, I would like to
say one thing, during Holi,
when you are buying any stock, be it for one day or
two days,
try to take a good stop
because if suppose your chart pattern,
your address, your strategy, if you go wrong, then at
least one good share will
remain in the portfolio and will give profit later too,
like this HDFC Ltd and
HDFC Bank, what do you think, it will
give more than these two stocks. No,
one day it will become a profit maker. Now sum it up
or friends, that's all the
information for now. If you liked it and found it useful, then
definitely like this video and if you are new to the channel, then
subscribe to this channel because
we keep updating about the share market on this
channel.  But keep bringing it, then we will meet
in the next video, till then goodbye.